(Azure Spring)
(All characters, places, events, etc. depicted are fictional.)
(Children and animals were filmed under strict guidelines.)
He killed someone?
It's probably some nonsense he said because he was drunk.
(Episode 5: How to Determine the End)
He must've been a soldier.
(Gun Accident in the Special Forces Guard Post)
(1 Dead, 1 Critically Injured)
"Gun accident in the special forces guard post."
(Staff Sergeant Yoon Faces 3 Years in Prison)
"Three years..."
"Critically injured"?
Yoon? Could it be...
Yoon Duk Hyun?
I thought you went out to feed the cats.
Yes, but I left my phone here.
I also couldn't find my phone, so I've been looking.
I'm sorry if that upset you.
Did you see it?
Is the Yoon here, who allegedly killed someone,
referring to you?
It's not, is it?
If it isn't you, just tell me so.
Don't leave me with the wrong idea.
It isn't.
It's not a misunderstanding.
I was in prison for three years...
for killing someone.
Why...
did you kill him?
Because he deserved to die.
Hey.
Hey!
What are you doing?
You seemed uncomfortable.
No...
It wasn't that.
I could tell by your eyes.
You can throw away my diving suit.
Where are you going, Duk Hyun?
Wait, are you leaving for good? All of a sudden?
What's with him?
Duk Hyun, are you really leaving?
Duk Hyun!
Who's this guy?
What do you think?
I'm with her.
You had an older brother?
Cha Jae Hun.
- What brings you here? - Surprised?
I'm surprised myself, too.
I can't believe I came to this hick town to see you.
Man.
I, Cha Jae Hun, must love you a lot, An Na.
What are you waiting for? Pack up.
I'll let you start all over again.
Swimming.
(Jung Gi Tae)
- Hey. - What's going on?
When I woke up, you were gone.
And so is that diver girl.
Enough.
Did you two run away together?
I did run away, but I don't know about her.
Did she hear what you said yesterday?
Me? What did I say?
Man, I always talk nonsense when I'm drunk.
It wasn't nonsense.
His death is practically on me.
She must be quite disappointed.
I am disappointed...
in myself.
- Jae Hun. - Hey. Hello?
- Did you really go there to get An Na? - Yes.
Why would you go after her?
You said you'd stop two-timing and only date me.
A return match between two former youth rivals.
It makes for a great story, doesn't it?
What are you going to do if I lose?
That's never going to happen.
I know An Na's swimming skills,
and she has nothing on you, Ye Gyeong.
Whatever. You figure it out, okay?
Darn it. Why is she being such a nuisance?
Let's start over, An Na.
How ridiculous.
I already know what Cha Jae Hun is like,
yet I returned immediately the moment he said...
I could start swimming again.
It's as if the days I spent...
in Parang-ri meant nothing.
That must've been over three minutes.
I held it for a while this time, didn't I?
It's not about how long you can hold your breath.
Then why are we doing this training?
To determine the end of your breath.
There's more to diving than holding your breath underwater.
You must know where it ends...
to let go, come up, and save yourself.
It's as if everything...
Yoon Duk Hyun said...
also did not...
mean anything.
(Seafood Ramyeon)
This isn't seafood ramyeon, but seafood-scented ramyeon.
What...
Gosh.
(Best before September 16th, 2024)
The end.
Who gets to determine that?
Darn it. Do we have to do this for Nam Sang Ho, too?
It's not for him. It's for Jae Hui.
But I'm the superior, not him.
Come on.
Ready or not, rock-paper-scissors.
Go now. Make them again.
Darn it.
- Make it quick! - Shut it.
Don't you see I have a freaking gun in my hand?
Hey, look.
- Please stop. - Scared, aren't you?
- Please stop. - Stop what?
That is dangerous.
Yes, you're in freaking danger right now.
Bang! And this will create a hole in your head.
So why won't you freaking listen while I'm being nice?
I told you to stop bullying him, didn't I?
Why are you so obsessed with harassing Jae Hui?
Why?
Did you ask why? There's no freaking reason.
It's fun.
You evil jerk.
Die.
Die!
Jae Hui... Jae Hui, no!
No, Jae Hui.
Jae Hui.
Jae Hui...
Jae Hui, no.
No, Jae Hui...
What the heck are you waiting for? Get help!
Jae Hui.
Gi Tae!
Jung Gi Tae!
What's going on?
Jae Hui... Jae Hui!
You nasty girl.
Ten years ago and even now, you haven't changed one bit.
Traitor.
Perhaps...
we do not know where our end is,
and that must be why we're holding on for dear life,
not realising we've already run out of breath.
Goodness.
I thought you had fled. Turns out you're waging a full-on war.
Hey, wake up.
Let's eat.
What has gotten into you?
I thought you'd never come here.
I came now, so I wouldn't have to come again.
You always pick out the worst things to say.
Remember that day on the island?
You asked why I was so hung up on you.
Did I?
Because I...
still can't forget the things...
that Jae Hui said.
Take your time, man. I won't take it from you.
It's so delicious.
He's really not the Special Forces type.
Don't you agree?
There's no particular type for that.
People get used to this life and make progress.
Gosh.
Actually, I...
joined the Special Forces because I wanted to change.
I didn't want to live like this anymore.
What's so bad about you?
Your bullies are the ones who did wrong.
Even so,
nothing would change if I didn't do anything.
I should...
at least try.
I want to pull you back out into the world,
and nothing would change if I sat around.
That is why...
I'm doing my best to try to convince you.
I'm sorry for doing this every time.
I don't have a bank account.
That's a lot.
Are you making a lump sum payment?
This is the last time.
You've been coming for two years,
but you went inside for the first time, right?
Many people do that.
It's not easy to face someone you love in such pain.
Well, something like that.
What was it like?
Didn't he say, "What took you so long?"
Come again.
We only accept a month's payment at a time.
I'm sorry. Please handle this for me.
(Haedam Convalescent Hospital)
I commend you for your courage.
It's not about being courageous.
I came to see where my end is.
- What the heck are you saying? - Settle down.
Stop chatting.
Let's start with a quick warm-up. Get ready.
Hey.
I heard you brought her back here.
- Are you kidding me? - Why not?
You had a thing for An Na, too.
Well, she's nice to look at.
But she has such a feisty personality.
Then just look at her.
If she's eye candy, that's enough.
Should I do that?
Gosh, my heart is racing.
Anyway, do you plan to let An Na...
get back into swimming?
No way.
She doesn't have what it takes to be an athlete.
Ye Gyeong hadn't been stepping up her game lately,
so it was to push her too.
"Too"?
It's been a while,
so I want to get in her pants, too.
Man, you're trash.
Ye Gyeong is sexy, and An Na is cute.
They're both my types.
To be honest, I already knew...
that this was the end for me.
I just...
haven't been able to let go.
I could've harvested it quickly.
And you could've died.
You must let it go and come back up.
That's how you'll live.
Just as Duk Hyun said,
will I live if I let this go?
Even after I quit swimming,
can I...
really live on?
Is one woman not enough for you?
Can you do that with both of them?
Hey, An Na.
Why did you stop?
Wait, where is she going? What?
What's wrong?
Are you unwell?
Is it your shoulder?
Darn it.
What the...
- Are you crazy? - Yes, I am crazy.
You can't keep swimming if you treat me like this.
I'm done, you jerk.
Seo An Na, you...
- Have you lost your mind? - What now?
I didn't say anything.
Darn it.
Hey, wait. It hurts.
I wasn't planning to sort this out with words, either.
Hey, Ye Gyeong.
If you keep flip-turning like that,
you'll end up like me.
Don't trust Coach Cha...
too much.
Gosh, I'm sorry.
I'll try to find the next tenant,
- so I'll pay one month's... - I understand.
Anyway, why is a young person like you suddenly moving to the countryside?
I must let everything go and go up to the surface before it's too late...
to live.
Yes, please do that.
Thank you.
Mom.
Am I really doing...
a good job?
Why do you even ask?
Goodness.
You weren't the type who'd do or drop everything...
as I suggested.
You never listened.
I wasn't like that.
I told you, didn't I?
It doesn't matter if the medal's gold or bronze.
They're all the same.
It doesn't matter whether you swim or not.
You're Seo An Na, Cho Mi Hyeon's daughter.
Live your life however you want to.
Eat a good meal and keep yourself warm.
Go live that life.
I'll always be here to support you.
Seo An Na, you can do it!
Do your job right, Su Jeong. Please!
I don't want to!
I should've been the one to go to Seoul, not An Na!
It's not too late.
What's going on? Why are you back already?
Yes, I'm back.
Have you been well?
After everything,
I'm back in Parang-ri.
But this time, it's different.
I'm now back on the surface.
That means I'm ready to dive back in.
I'm hungry.
You're here, too.
Have you been...
waiting for me?
I came because I had one last thing to say.
If it's an explanation about your past,
I don't want to hear it.
I didn't look it up,
and I'm not curious.
If you really were a bad person,
the police would've taken you away already.
Above all,
you don't owe me an apology...
or need my forgiveness for it.
You should...
go back to swimming.
I came because I wanted to tell you that.
Can I really live on even after I quit swimming?
I was afraid.
You know you're being funny right now, right?
I realised it as I watched you harvest seafood.
You can start over.
How dare an amateur judge an athlete?
My apologies.
I shouldn't have been so nosy.
But I'm no longer afraid.
I'm glad you look fine.
Then, please excuse me.
Do you want...
to swim together?
This time,
I'll teach you.
Because I know we have each other,
who would willingly jump...
into the water together.
What? How did you find me here?
Come on. I've been stalking Duk Hyun for three years.
Finding a well-known swimmer was a piece of cake.
What do you want?
It's about Yoon Duk Hyun.
It seemed like he returned to that island.
He left without looking back. I doubt it.
I'm certain.
So,
when you meet him again,
make sure...
you pull him out of the water.
I noticed him smiling...
when he was with you.
My goodness!
Hey!
He smiled when he was with me?
Wake up!